Welcome to our Magical Kingdom
2025 a night up on the mix of
[Applause]
[Music]
hello with the extending network of BS I
believe they are able to reach out to
more Malaysian provide more protection
help all Malaysian with their health and
protection needs I look forward to the
greatest Success With all you for 20
[Music]
fight wishing everyone good health
vitality and Achieve
[Music]
again we have celebrated in a very
fashionable way thank you to all worker
BSN know you guys are the reasons why we
are all here tonight This Night Belongs
to all of
[Music]
you let us all congratulate to both of
our winners for the incredible
achievements tonight
[Music]
this is the place for us to celebrate
all of you this platform is yours to
desel I am pled to play my part in
letting you show your brillance and thck
Center Station
[Music]